Where does comedy come from?
Comedian is a comedy, documentary film directed by Christian Charles.
A look at the work of two stand-up comics, Jerry Seinfeld and a lesser-known newcomer, detailing the effort and
frustration behind putting together a successful act and career while living a life on the road.
Self, played by Jerry Seinfeld.
Self, played by Orny Adams.
Self, played by Greg Giraldo.
Self, played by Jim Norton.
Self, played by Sherrod Small.
Self, played by Allan Havey.
Comedian is a 2002 American documentary film focused primarily on comedian
Jerry Seinfeld as he develops a new stand-up comedy act.
The tone is lighthearted.